var quizKey = {
	questions:[
		{type: "mc" ,question: "Which of these was Mozart's middle name?",answers: ["Wolfgangus", "Homer", "Amadeus" ,"Johannes"], key: "Wolfgangus"},
		{type: "mc",question: "On a clear night about how many galaxies are visible to the naked eye?",answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], key: "2"},
		{type: "mc",question: "How many muscles do you have in total in all your fingers combined?",answers: ["0", "10", "22", "25"], key: "0"},
		{type: "mc",question: "How many toes does a two toed sloth have?",answers: ["0", "2", "4", "6 or 8"], key: "6 or 8"},
		{type: "mc",question: "Which of the following characters are rabbits?",answers: ["Bugs Bunny", "Easter Bunny", "Bher Rabbit", "None"], key: "None"},
		{type: "mc",question: "How many man made artifacts on Earth can be seen from space?",answers: ["Zero", "One", "Hundreds", "Thousands"], key: "Thousands"},
		{type: "mc",question: "What was Billy the Kid's real first name?",answers: ["Henry", "William", "Bill", "Kidd"], key: "Henry"},
		{type: "mc",question: "What kind of animal is the longest in the world?",answers: ["Snake", "Jellyfish", "Worm", "Whale"], key: "Worm"},
		{type: "mc",question: "Which of these animals was the first to be domesticated?",answers: ["Horse", "Cat", "Dog", "Reindeer"], key: "Reindeer"},
		{type: "mc",question: "How many actors played Harry Potter in the Harry Potter movies?",answers: ["1", "2", "4", "8"], key: "4"}
	]
};

export default quizKey;